Time for the Game to Begin!
早く早く！
Hurry! Hurry up!
（ホイッスル）
（審判）それでは　これより
聖石舞祭石矢魔対→
And now, St. Ishiyama Festival presents,
an exhibition match between Ishiyama and
St. Ishiyama representatives. Let us begin!
聖石矢魔部長連のエキシビションマッチを
開催する。両チーム整列！
Both teams, line up!
（歓声）
（古奈）お待たせいたしました！→
Thank you for your patience! Presenting
the Ishiyama festival's main event!
今年の聖石舞祭注目の目玉企画！
六騎聖対　石矢魔問題児→
A volleyball match between the Six
Holy Knights and Ishiyama's JD Squad!
集団による　バレー対決！わたくし
司会進行を務めさせて頂きます→
Broadcaster
I have been requested by the
committee to do play-by-play.
放送部の古奈多依子と申します。
そして解説は→
Furuna Taeko of the Broadcast Club.
An our color commentator is former
volleyball club member, Hatakeyama-sempai!
元バレー部の畑山先輩！
（畑山）ちょっと待って！→
Hold up a sec, 'kay? I'm
getting in character!
今　キャラ作るから。
あ　はい…。
Um... Right.
元々は　生徒同士のいさかいから
始まった　この勝負！→
The origins of this match drew
from a conflict between students.
六騎聖は　その権限を　そして
石矢魔に至っては　何と退学を！
The Six Holy Knights risk
their authorization!
And for Ishiyama, a loss
means no less than expulsion!
それぞれ譲れないものを
賭けてます！
So each cannot afford to lose!
（畑山）ニャー！
Meow!
えっ！そのキャラで
いくんですか？
Eh? That's your character?
ニャ！
盛り上げる気　ありますよね？
Meow!
You are up for this broadcast, aren't you?
ニャ！ニャ！
Meow! Meow!
Oh! Both teams are glaring at the other!
お～っと！並んだ両チーム
早くも　にらみ合う！
会長　たのみますよ～！
Mr. Club President, we're all behind you!
不良なんか　軽く
ひねっちゃって下さ～い！
They're just delinquents!
Run up the score for us!
≪出馬センパーイ！≫
Izuma-sempai!
Shi-zu-ka! Shi-zu-ka!
（出馬）ハハ…
礼を言わせてもらうで。
We really must thank you.
（東条）あ？
君らのおかげで→
Thanks to you people, this year's St.
Ishiyama festival has been a smashing success.
今年の聖石舞祭は大成功や。
（姫川）知るかボケ。
（神崎）何もしてねえし。
What'cha talkin' about?
We didn't do nothin'!
（出馬）いやいや　実際君らが
悪役やってくれるから→
No, seriously. With you playing
the part of the bad guys,
僕らもこうして　支持してもらえる
ようになったんやし。→
the student body is
supporting us for a change.
今までは　どっちかってゆうと
怖がられてたからな。
Up until now, they were more
afraid of us than anything else.
今日は　よろしく。お互い
最高の試合にしようや。
So thanks for today. Let's give them
the best game they've ever seen.
（邦枝）そうね。でも　大成功っていう
には　気が早いんじゃない？
You may be right.
But I think you're counting this as a
"smashing success" a little too early.
（古奈）ここで両チーム
キャプテンが握手！→
And we have the handshake between captains!
おっ　意外にも不良チーム
これに応じます。
I never expected the delinquent
team to accept a sporting gesture!
ギャー　出馬さんに…。
さわんな　石矢魔！
Nooo! Not Izuma-san!
Don't touch them, Ishiyama!
そして大ブーイング！いやぁ
畑山さん　彼らにも→
Now jeers from the crowd!
Well, Hataykeama-san, do you think those
delinquents possess a trace of sportsmanship?
スポーツマンシップは
あるのでしょうか？
にゃ～っ？
振った私がバカでした。
さあ　両チーム→
I was a fool to even ask.
And with pre-game formalities done,
each team takes their positions!
一礼の後　コートに
わかれます。
（神崎）おい審判
さっさと始めようぜ。
Hey, Ref! Let's get this thing started.
あ　あの…。→
Um... You intend to play the game like that?
そのままで試合するんですか？
（男鹿）あ？
（ベル坊）アダブ？
審判　もっともな疑問だ！
よく言いました。
The Ref brings up a very pertinent
question. Well said, sir!
正直　私もつっこむべきか
非常に迷うところでした。
To tell the truth, I was wondering whether
to make sarcastic comments myself!
ダメなのか？
ブー！
It's against the rules?
いや　ダメっていうか…逆に
いいんですか？それで。
"Against the rules"? What I'm asking
is are you sure you want to?
（アレックス）フ…愚問ですよ　審判。
Such a silly question, sir.
彼はケンカの最中も子供を
離さない　子育て番長ですよ。
He's the Baby on Board Brawler who won't
even put down the child for a fight.
（七海）えらいわねぇ。でも
何でハダカ？
I'm impressed. But why is he nude?
Unexpectedly, they aren't objecting!
意外と受け入れられている～！！
まあ　両チーム異論がないなら
問題ないです。
W-Well... If neither team has an
objection, then I'll allow it.
（古奈）そして通った～！
Now it's legal!
うぃ～！
（ヒルダ）坊っちゃま！
（古奈）さあ　それでは
両チーム　よろしいですね？→
Master!
So, everything is settled
between the two sides.
ただ今より　六騎聖対
石矢魔による　バレーボール→
Let the Six Holy Knights vs. Ishiyama,
three-set exhibition
volleyball match... begin!
エキシビション　３セットマッチ
試合開始です！
（ホイッスル）
（古奈）最初のサーブは　六騎聖。
打つのは→
First serve goes to the Six Holy Knights.
Star of the boxing club, Shinjo serving!
ボクシング部主将　新庄選手！
フッ！
お～！
にゃ～！
何と　新庄選手！バレー部員ですら
出来る者は少ないという→
Shinjo is amazing!
The "spike serve" is rare even among
volleyball club members, but he did it with ease!
スパイクサーブを　いとも簡単に！
にゃ…オレの努力は
何だったんだよ。
If you take my lines, why am I here?
そのキャラ
しゃべっていいんすか？→
Your character can talk?!
これは石矢魔　きびしいか～！？
Is it too much serve for Ishiyama to return?
≪お～！≫
（夏目）姫ちゃん！
おう！
Hime-chan!
どや～っ！！
ハッ！
チッ！
（古奈）ブ　ブロックー！→
Th-They blocked it!
まずは六騎聖が先制！しかし
石矢魔の流れも悪くない！
The Six Holy Knights take the initiative,
but Ishiyama proves to be no pushover!
東条！
ん？
Tojo.
フッ…。
（古奈）さあ新庄選手
またもジャンプサーブ！→
Now Shinjo does another jump serve!
そして邦枝選手　難なく
これを拾う。からの～！
And somehow Kunieda managed to dig it out!
It goes to...
男鹿～！！
ヨォ！
Oga!
ターッ！
≪え…≫
≪あ～…≫
Husssh...
ヨッシャー！
ヒャー！
（ホイッスル）
反則！
Foul.
え？
アダブ！
Why?!
あったり前でしょうが～！
バスケじゃないんだから！
What else did you expect?!
This isn't basketball!
（古奈）
さあ　盛り上がってまいりました！
１セット目も中盤にさしかかり→
Now the crowd is really revved up!
We're nearing the mid-point of the first
set, and a slight lead has opened up!
わずかに点差が開いてきたが～…
リードしているのは六騎聖です！
With the ones in the lead
being the Six Holy Knights!
なかなか　やるじゃねえか。
ああ。俄然　燃えてきたぜ。
Those jerks got some skills.
Suddenly I'm all fired up!
いや　負けてんのは
あんた達のせいだから。
Yeah, but... You two are
the reason we're losing.
え？
え？は？
ギャッ！
言ってる意味が　分からん。
もう少し　分かりやすく。
You're not making sense.
Explain using simple words!
埋めたり　つかんだり　隠したり
飛び越えたりを→
Don't cover the ball, hold the ball, hide
the ball, or jump the net. Simple enough?
やめろって言ってんのよ！
破裂させたりは？
ダメに決まってんでしょ！
Busting the ball?
No! What'd you expect?
（東条・男鹿）あ～っ！！
てめえら　ふざけんなよ。
何だと！→
Cut the crap, you creeps!
What was that?! You wanna
take me on? Any time, pal!
やるんなら　いつでも
相手になるぜ！
反則は　バレねえようにやらないと
意味ねえだろ。
What good is it to commit a foul
when you're doing it so obviously?
どマヌケどもが！！
You utter fools!
≪え～…≫
（東条・男鹿）お～っ！
いや　そういうこと…。
石矢魔チーム
早く始めてください！
No... That isn't the point...
Ishiyama Team, let's get the game going.
あ…はい！
Yes, sir!
タイムだ　審判。
We need a time-out, Ref.
お～っと　石矢魔チーム
ここでタイムアウト！
Whoa! Ishiyama team takes a time out here!
どうぞ　先輩。
タオルあるわよ。
Here you go, Sempai!
We've got towels too.
出馬くん　ひとつ
聞きたいんだけど。
Izuma-kun, I have a question for you.
なんや？怖いな～
静さんは。
What now? You can be scary, Shizuka-san.
ちゃんと考えてあるんでしょうね
このあとのこと。
You've made provisions for what
happens afterwards, right?
あの子　生半可な流れじゃ
納得しないわよ。
That boy won't accept any half-baked excuses.
あ～　そのことかいな。
さて　どうやろな？
Oh, you mean that!
Now, whatever shall I do?
ちょっと　出馬くん！
Come on, Izuma-kun!
ま　何にせよ
今が楽しければ　いいんちゃうん？
Well, whatever happens. As long
as we're having fun now, right?
まだまだ何か　やってくれそうや彼らは…。
Besides, I'm sure they'll do our work for us!
あいた。もう静さんには
かなわんわ。暴力反対やで。
Ow!
I can never match up to you,
Shizuka-san. No violence, right?
（郷）フ…素人がいると
楽で良いな。
I love it when we play amateurs.
勝手に自滅してくれるぜ。
ええ。どうやら彼ら→
They'll self-destruct for us.
After all, they don't even know the rules.
ルールすら
分かってないようですからね。
何だよ　結局
点差ひらいて来てんじゃん。
What's the deal? Now
they're opening up a lead!
な。やっぱ不良なんて
しょせん　この程度だよな。
体力ね～んじゃね。
Yeah, that's only natural when
you're playing delinquents.
They got no stamina!
（歓声）
さあタイムアウトが終了しました。
Now, the time out has come to an end!
両チーム　ポジションに戻ります。
And both teams take their positions!
（ホイッスル）
（古奈）石矢魔チームは　一体→
So what new plan has the
Ishiyama team come up with?
どんな作戦を
立てて来たんでしょうか？
（歓声）
（一同）フフフ…。
何？
What?
い～から　とっとと打てよ。おう！来いや　こら。
ブ～ブ～。
Never mind. Just go and serve!
Yeah, come on!
（三木）《何を企んでる。
まさか　また反則を…》
What are they plotting? Not another foul?
反則ってのは　ルールを破るから
反則になるんだ。俺たちには→
A foul is only a foul if it breaks the rules.
But we have a special rule that
was made especially for us.
俺たちだけに許された
特別ルールがあるだろう？
邦枝！
まかせて！
Kunieda!
It's mine!
（古奈）レシーブ上がった！
（姫川）よし　行くぞ！
Receiver! It's yours!
Right! Here we go!
《あ…連携》
（古奈）おおっと　これは？
A combination attack?
Whoa! What's this?!
おいおい　まさか
そんな高等技術。
Hey, they can't be using
that advanced an attack!
（古奈）男鹿選手
夏目選手の前に跳び→
Oga dashes in front of
Natsume to hide the set!
トスを隠した～。
（三木）《どっちだ…》
Which one?
後ろ　男鹿です！
な…。→
From behind! It'll be Oga!
Wha...?
何と　男鹿選手
後ろからボールを→
It seems Oga was set up from behind
and is going on the attack!
そのままアタック～！
（榊）乙。
Fail.
（郷）ボールじゃ…ない。
ニン。
That's not the...
...ball!
ゴールデン…。
ニ～。
Golden...
ボール。
ニ～。
...ball.
は…。
（歓声）
（古奈）
入った～！何という汚い
いや　頭脳プレーでしょうか。→
It's in bounds!
What a dirty... er... smart play!
石矢魔チーム
７人目の選手である赤ん坊を→
Ishiyama used their seventh
player, the baby, a decoy!
ダミーに使って来ました！
は　反則だ審判。あんなプレーが
許される訳ない！
Th-That's a foul, Ref! There's
no way that play can be allowed!
おいおい　言い掛かりはよせよ。
最初に　そのガキを→
Hey, quit it with the false accusations.
At the very start, you accepted Oga
and the kid both as a single player.
男鹿の一部として認めたのは
テメーらだぜ。
ルール的には
何の問題もね～だろ。
So there isn't a rule in
the world preventing that.
あると思うけど…。
I'm pretty sure there is...
Father/Son Time Delay!
Baby Block!
（古奈）そして…。
And the Golden Pacifier of Mystery!
凄い　凄すぎます！まさにスーパー赤ちゃん！
Amazing! Far too amazing!
That is truly a super baby!
もはやバレーじゃねえ！
This isn't volleyball anymore!
誰が　こんな展開を
予想したでしょうか。→
Who could have predicted
a twist such as this!
卑怯を通り越して　清々しさすら
感じます。
あの子　かわい。
It's gone beyond "cheating" and
into "refreshing" territory!
That kid is so cute!
がんばれ～。
（古奈）
石矢魔のセットポイントです。
Go little sweetie!
It's set point for Ishiyama!
よっしゃ　いけるぜ！
おうよ！
ダイダブ。
Yes! We can do this!
That's right!
く…。
まずいわね。
This could be bad.
来い！
（古奈）さあ　これが１セット目。→
Come on!
Is this the very final
rally of the first set?
最後のラリーとなるのか？
な…。
アカンわ。もう　アカンアカン。
１セット目は→
Can't have that.
No, we certainly can't.
I was going to give you a normal
volleyball game for the first set.
普通のバレーしとこ思ってたのに
君らのせいやで…。
So what happens now is your fault.
（静）＜出雲八神流　発祥は→
The Izuma Eight-God School.
They say it was a fighting sword technique
from the Warring States Period.
戦国時代の古武術と
言われているけれど→
But when it incorporated
elements of Baji Quan,
八極拳を取り込む事で
独自の進化を→
it evolved into a unique
school of martial arts.
遂げた流派ね。発頸を用い→
It has a wide variety of attacks
that make use of Hakkei to heighten
the power to its upper limits.
一撃の威力を極限まで高めた
その技の数々は　もちろん→
Of course, it was never intended
to be used in volleyball.
バレーボールをする為のものでは
ないけど＞
は。
な。
何と…。
Look at that!
ぐ…。
Heavy!
《重》
あ～。
（ざわめき）
And another serve too powerful to dig out!
またも　無茶苦茶なサーブが
出ました！→
That brings the first set to an end!
ここで１セット目終了！
取ったのは六騎聖。
And the winners are the Six Holy Knights!
（邦枝）つ…。
あ～すげえ赤くなっちゃってるね。
Your arms have really gotten red.
Are you all right?
大丈夫？
ええ。
Yes.
That four-eyed cretin.
What is with that serve?
あのクソ眼鏡　なんちゅうサーブ打ちやがる。
You really should give
those arms some time off.
（由加）こりゃ～１回休んだ方がいいっすね。
Madam Aoi, bet you can't even lift your arms.
葵姐さん　腕あがんないっしょ。
She's right. Furuichi! Fill in for a while.
（寧々）そうね…古市
アンタしばらく交代よ。
（古市）ええ！いやいや…無理っすよ。
No, no, no, no! Impossible! I'd die!
死ぬっすよ。あんなサーブ
取れる訳ないじゃないっすか。→
There's no way I could
return a serve like that!
That was a serve that even
Kunieda-sempai couldn't dig out!
邦枝先輩にも取れなかった
サーブっすよ。そんなもん俺が…。
You think I could...
アンタの為の　すんごい応援
見たくない？
Don't you want to see the really
amazing cheer I came up with for you?
((古市！))
Furuichi!
（２人）((古市！))
（３人）((古市！))
Furuichi!
Yes, amazing!
《すんごい…》
やります。
Of course I'll stand in.
We're beginning Set 2!
（古奈）さあ　第２セットが
始まりました。→
It's do or die for Ishiyama!
もう後がない石矢魔。果たして
逆転は出来るのか！
But can they turn this around?!
おおっと　石矢魔チーム
選手を代えて来ましたね。→
Look, the Ishiyama team
has made a substitution!
邦枝選手に代わり
入ったのは古市選手。→
Substituting for Kunieda is Furuichi!
なぜ最初から
ドヤ顔なんでしょうか。
What's with the "how do
you like me now" face?!
フン…アイツの扱いが分かって来ましたよ。
I've figured out how to manipulate him!
In any case, until we find a way
to return that serve, we can't win!
《とにかく　あのサーブを
攻略しないと勝てない。→
Just hold out until the numbness
in my arms goes away! Everybody!
腕のシビレが治るまで
頼むわよ　皆》
Here I go!
行くぜ。
はあ～！えい。
There's Furuichi with a weak underhand serve!
（古奈）古市選手　地味に
アンダーサーブ！→
六騎聖　流れるような連携で
これを返す。
The Six Holy Knights follow
up with a set and spike!
おい。
マ。
Hey!
Kunieda, I shall ask a question of you.
邦枝　つかぬ事を聞くが…。
What do you think of that man?
あの男の事　どう思う？
ええ　突然！
All of a sudden...
古市バカ！
Furuichi, idiot!
"That man."
W-Well, what do you think of him?
あ　あなたこそ
どうなのよ？
Are you really that concerned a-about him?
こんな学校まで押しかけて
そんなに気になるの？
彼の事…。
まあな。
Yes.
Of course, that man is not my only concern.
別に
あの男だけという訳ではないが。
はあ？
That man Izuma has a power that
ordinary men do not possess.
《あの出馬という男　確かに
並外れた力を持っているが…。→
However, is it the power of demons?
果たして　それが
悪魔の力によるものか→
Presently I sense no demonic power.
今の所　魔力は感じないが…》
（邦枝）わ　私は。
I-I have to say that I am... concerned.
気には　なってるかも…。
Maybe.
あ！いや…その　ほらあれよ。
But it isn't... You know! Like...
I mean, like any good classmate!
いいクラスメイトとしてって意味よ。別に→
It isn't like I'm in l-l-l-l-l-love
or anything like that!
すすす…好きとか
そういう事じゃないんだから。
I admit it's fun being with him...
そりゃ一緒にいるのは楽しいけど。そ　それだって→
B-But I just mean in a sense of like,
being with everybody, you know?
皆と一緒にって意味で。
《あ　そうか。→
I see.
こうやって皆で
バレーの試合したりとか→
This is the first time we've ever done
something like play volleyball all together like this.
今まで　なかったし…。
負けたら退学。→
But if we lose... expulsion?
私　このクラスを
終わらせたくない》
I don't want to see this
class come to an end.
（歓声）
（古奈）入った～！
また入りました。→
It's in! Another one gets by him!
凄い　凄すぎます！
出馬選手が止まらない！→
Incredible! Just too incredible!
No one can stop Izuma! He's a monster! Just
what a student-body president should be!
まさに怪物！さすが生徒会長！→
点差は開く一方です。
Their lead has gone from big to one-sided!
これは石矢魔　厳しいか～？
Is Ishiyama on their last legs?
早くも勝負がつきそうですね～。
It seems our match is drawing to a close.
久しぶりにしゃべりましたね。
畑山さん。
It's been a while since we heard from you.
Hatakeyama-san. But how about
saying something original.
つ～か普通ですか？
（姫川）全員ザルだ。
You all are just apes!
Says the worst of us all!
てめえが一番ひでえクセに。あ～？
やんのか？コラァ。んだとコラァ！
Ya wanna go, punk?
What was that?
（邦枝）やめなさい！
（姫川・神崎）あ！？
Stop it!
（古奈）おおっと！ここでリべロが
交代のようですね。
It seems the libero is
putting herself back in!
邦枝…。
お前　もういいのか？
Kunieda?
Are you healed up?
みんな聞いて！
今から全部のボール→
Everyone, listen up!
I'm going to dig out every ball from now on.
Every one. Every one! So you guys...
私が拾って拾って拾いまくるわ！
だから…。
絶対　勝つわよ！
We're going to win this!
ダ～ブダ～！
（一同）お～！
（古奈）おおっと　なんでしょう？→
Oh! What just happened?!
石矢魔チーム
急に気合が入りました！
Suddenly the Ishiyama team
looks set and determined!
I admit it. Your serve is incredible.
（邦枝）《確かに　あなたのサーブはすごいわ。→
まともに対峙すれば
ふるえる程の圧力》
Its power, once felt, is
enough to make me tremble!
But...
《でも…》
《ヒルダさん程じゃ…ない！》
But you don't hold a candle to... Hilde-san!
うわあああ！
（古奈）あ　上がった～！
Sh-She dug it out!
This is the first time anyone has
manged to field Azuma's serve!
初めて出馬選手のサーブが
上がりました～！
ようし　来い！
Right! Come on!
また赤ん坊を使ったフェイクか！
いつまでも　そんな手が…！
Are you trying to decoy
us again with that kid?!
I can't be fooled twice!
高い！
よっしゃぁぁ！
ダァ！
What a jump!
ぐあああ！
小細工は　なしだ。
To hell with complicated strategy!
な…！くっ！
Wha--?
（古奈）さあ　そして石矢魔の攻撃は続きます。→
And Ishiyama's attack shows no let-up!
夏目選手に～。
From Natsume...
ぐおお！
（古奈）東条選手！→
...to Tojo!
邦枝選手がまた拾う！
Kunieda digs out another!
Then to Kanzaki...
（古奈）神崎選手に～そして
姫川選手！…って誰！？
...to Himekawa!
Wait! Who?!
Way to go!
やったやった！
Is it just my imagination, Hatakeyama-san?
気のせいでしょうか？畑山さん→
石矢魔チームの動きが
急に良くなったようですが。
Or is the Ishiyama team suddenly
looking much better than before?
いやぁ　すごいですにゃ～。
Well, they are ameowzing!
I think you've finally gotten your character.
なんかキャラ完成しましたね。
（古奈）気合が入ると強くなる。
これぞ　まさに不良だ。→
Once you get into the fight, you get
stronger! Isn't that the essence of street punks?
といったところでしょうか。
（畑山）だったら最初から
やれって感じですよにゃ。
Maybe that's what happened.
If so, then get meow-tivated from the start!
フン…ようやく一つになったか。
They have finally combined to become one.
ていうか石矢魔　普通に強くない？
Wait a minute? Isn't Ishiyama,
like, a good team?
不良だと思ってナメてたけど。
I just dismissed them as delinquents, but...
That long-hair looks kinda cool!
あのロン毛　カッコイイかも～！
≪いいぞ～いいぞ～石矢魔！≫
≪やるじゃね～か！≫
Go, go! Ishiyama!
You're pretty good!
I'll root for you!
≪感動した～≫
≪どっちも頑張れ～！≫
≪子連れ番長～！≫
Hang in there, both teams!
BoB Brawler!
You can work as a team!
≪チームワーク
あるじゃねえか！≫
≪くっにえっださ～ん！≫
Kunieda-san!
Ladies and gentlemen, just
listen to this crowd!
な～んと！お聞き下さい。この歓声！
私ちょっと目頭が
熱くなってまいりました。
I can't help it! I'm moved to tears!
Now with the points differential
reversed, it's Ishiyama's set point!
（古奈）
さあ　ついに点差は逆転し
石矢魔のセットポイントです。
大変なことに
なってまいりました！
What an unbelievable reversal!
Not an inch of wriggle room for either team!
両者　一歩も譲らぬ激しい攻防！
得点は２７対２８！石矢魔
５回目のマッチポイントです！
Our score: 27 to 28!
It is now Ishiyama's fifth match point!
（一同）ハァハァ…。
チッ！
Oh, no! Himekawa's serve got away from him!
お～っと姫川選手
サーブが乱れました！
I see their endurance is running meowt.
さすがに体力の限界
にゃのでしょう。
It looks like an opportunity
for the Six Holy Knights!
（古奈）
さあ　六騎聖　チャンスボールです。
Go! Decide this thing now!
行け～！決めてくれ～！
Izuma with a full-body spike!
（古奈）
出馬選手　渾身のスパイク！→
And it's blocked!
ブロック！弾いた～！→
邦枝選手　これを追うが～…→
Kunieda is going after it,
but she'll never make it!
間に合わない！
よし！
Yes!
さすが出馬さん！
That's Izumo-san for you!
な　なんと男鹿選手！ポジションを無視してこれに食らい付いている。
Wh-What?! It's Oga!
He left his position and is
trying to field the ball!
メリコミ！アターック！
Burying Attack!
It...
（古奈）は　入った～！
It's in bounds!
（歓声）
（古奈）入りました！→
It counts!
まさかの返球にチーム六騎聖
一歩も動けず！
An unbelievable return shot left the
Six Holy Knights frozen in place!
Final Score: 27 to 29!
２７対２９！！→
エキシビジョンマッチ
バレーボール大会を→
The winners of this volleyball
exhibition match are,
制したのは　なんと石矢魔です！
none other than the Ishiyama team!
よっしゃ～！
All right!
アハハ！やりましたよ！寧々さん！
うん！
They did it, Nene-san!
（古奈）これで石矢魔の退学は
白紙になりました～！
And with this, the Ishiyama
students' expulsion is rescinded!
The Master...
よっしゃ～！
Yes!
Dammit!
くそ！三木。
Miki...
すいません。僕の…僕のせいです。
Forgive me! It's... It's my fault!
僕が　あいつの動きをちゃんと見てれば。
If I had watched his movements...
ば～か　チームで
戦ったんだろうが。
Dummy! We play as a team, right?
フッ…。
（邦枝）立てる？ん？
Can you stand?
あなたには　いつも
驚かされるわね。
You always seem to surprise me.
フッ。
（審判）両チーム整列！
Both teams, come to the center!
That was terrific!
≪すごかったぞ～！≫
≪石矢魔おめでとう～！≫
Ishiyama, congratulations!
And the Six Holy Knights
made a good showing too!
六騎聖もいい試合だったぞ～！
やれやれ…負けてしもたな～。
Well, well...
It seems we lost.
邦枝さんか…覚えとくで。
君には完敗や。
You're Kunieda?
I'll remember you. It's you I lost to.
いい試合だったわ。
またやりましょう。
It was a good game. Let's
do it again sometime.
No way!
（夏目・神崎・姫川）やだよ。
And you. You're Oga-kun, right?
そっちの君も…
男鹿くん　言うたか？
久也が目の敵にすんのも
よう分かるわ。
I can see why Hisaya is so
anxious to get revenge on you.
まぁ君らには　まだこれから…。
Well, your turn is coming up soon...
（古奈）あっちょっ…！
なんですか　あなたは。
Wait! What do you think you're doing?!
（邦枝・ベル坊・男鹿）あ。
Give me back my mic! Hey!
（古奈）
返してください。ちょっと～！
（霧矢）スポーツを通じて一致団結。流れる汗。ほとばしる情熱。
All are equals on the sports field.
All drench themselves in sweat.
All overflow with passion!
What's with him?!
なんだ？あいつ。
（霧矢）お互い死力を尽くして
戦ったその先には→
And when one's desperate efforts
have been left on the field,
もう一切のわだかまりもなく→
Enmity is left there as well.
いつしか認め合い　１つになる聖石矢魔と石矢魔…ってか？
And all that's left is the mutual
respect of Ishiyama and St. Ishiyama.
Is that the deal?
（霧矢）クソ似合わね～こと
してんじゃね～ぞ！男鹿！
That crap don't suit you,
so don't do it, Oga!
It's him!
あいつは…！
あっ！
フフヘヘヘ…。
This is bad, Oga! Kiriya's back
and he's coming after you!
Don't he ever learn?
You gotta just take it, Oga! You won the
match, so if you fight here, it's expulsion again!
Now is when Oga's secret past is
revealed! And the truth about Miki too!
Oh?! Oga's secret past, you say?!
Next time on Beelzebub:
Finally, the Deciding Battle!
And what of the forbidden
love between Oga and Miki?!
"F-Forbidden love"?!
Nothing like that in the story.